What do you do to care for yourself?
Talk a lot of shit with Regina.
I affirm myself on a daily basis.
I actually do affirmations.
That's how I start my day.
And at the end of my day, I give thanks for all the wonderful things that I have in my life.
Yeah, I walk a lot.
I'm like the Indian forest gum.
I swear, I'm like everywhere, like all over the place, on foot, listening to shit 80s music.
What do you do, Amanda?
I would love to.
What do you do?
You know, first of all, I lie to myself.
So we'll start there.
I lie to myself and I'm like, I'm great.
I'm fine.
I have an endless capacity for all of this.
I can manage everything.
And then I'm like, but boy, my lower back really hurts.
And it's because, yes, fool, you're holding all of it in your lower inside back.